Hastings, James F.; Papers apap254
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- New York State Legislature, 1956-1968; Undated; 2; 2.47 cubic ft.
  - Medicinal Narcotics Facts on Benefits and Controls, 1965 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - New York State Technical Services Program Pamphlet, 1965 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - State of New York Conservation Department (Preliminary) Fifty-Fourth Annual Report for 1964, 1965 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Fair Text Book Bill, 1965; 1967 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Chautauqua County Education, 1965-1966 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Divorce Laws, 1965-1966 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Electronic Voting, 1965-1966 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Ischua Creek Watershed, 1965-1966 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Legislation Correspondence (1 of 2), 1965-1966 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Legislation Correspondence (2 of 2), 1965-1966 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Jamestown Legislation, 1965-1966; 1968 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - University Review, A Publication of the State University of New York, Volume 1, 1966 Fall (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - 21 Year Drinking Age, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - 1967 Constitutional Convention, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Annual Report - New York State Police, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Annual Report of the Superintendent of Banks, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Annual Report State Advisory Council on Employment and Unemployment Insurance, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Cattaraugus and Chautauqua County Teachers Association, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Chautauqua County Board of Supervisors, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Chautauqua County Capitol Construction, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Committee Agriculture and Marketing, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Committee Authorities, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Criminal Procedure Law Arts. 1-105 Tentative Draft, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Hanover Harbor Improvement District, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Legislation Correspondence, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Legislation on Aging in New York State, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Memorandum - Repeal of Railroad Law Sections 54-a and 54-c, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - National Defense Committee, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - New York State Atomic and Space Development Authority Annual Report and Nuclear Fuel Services, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - New York State Revenue Endangered by Adverse Legislation Affecting the State's Largest Corporate Product of Revenue - Corrective Action Recommend, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - Personal and Employment Characteristics of Professional Nurses Registered in New York State, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - Press Releases, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - Report of the New York State Science and Technology Foundation, 1966 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - State of New York Governor's Special Committee on Criminal Offenders General Work Plan - II, 1966 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Town of Dunkirk Water District, 1966 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Youth and Correction Legislation in New York State, 1966 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - City of Dunkirk, 1966; Undated (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Lottery Amendment, 1966; Undated (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - New York Business Development Corporation - A Report of a Decade of Operation… 1966, Undated (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - 1967 Proposed Legislation, 1966-1967 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Ambulance Service, 1966-1967; Undated (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Joint Legislative Committee to Revise and Simplify Education Law (1 of 2), 1966-1967; Undated (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Joint Legislative Committee to Revise and Simplify Education Law (2 of 2), 1966-1967; Undated (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Soil and Water Conservation District, 1966-1968 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Valley View Nursing Home Correspondence, 1966-1968 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Ninth Annual Report of the Temporary Commission of Investigation of the State of New York to the Governor and the Legislature of the State of New York, 1967 February (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - State of New York - The Judicial Conference Report in Relation to the Civil Practice Law and Rules, 1967 February (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - A Study of a Metropolitan New York Transportation, 1967 March (Flat-file 3)
  - State of New York - Administrative Board of the Judicial Conference Report in Relation to Recommendations for Increased Judicial Manpower, 1967 March (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - A.B.C. Laws (Alcoholic Beverage Control Law), 1967 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Fine Arts Center B.O.C.E.S. and St. Bonaventure University, 1967 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - High Schools for a Changing World, 1967 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Jetports and General Aviation in the New York Metropolitan Area, 1967 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Joint Legislative Committee to Revise and Simplify the Education Law, 1967 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Know Your Legislators, 1967 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Motor Vehicle Statistical Summary, 1967 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Office of Legislative Research - Misused Statistics on the State's Economy and Educational Ranking, 1967 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Position of the Hospital Association of New York State on Nursing Education, 1967 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Sales Tax, 1967 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - State of New York Court of Claims Annual Report to Governor Rockefeller, 1967 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - State of New York Message to the Legislature and Inaugural Address Nelson A. Rockefeller, 1967 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Studies of Public School Support 1966 Series, 1967 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Summary of Governor Rockefeller's 1967 Message to the Legislature (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Third Interim Report and Correspondence on the Electric Power Failure of November 9, 1965, 1967 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Transportation Bond Issue, 1967 (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Water Resources Classification, 1967 (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - West Valley School Correspondence, 1967 (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Cattaraugus County Resolutions, 1967-1968 (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - Chautauqua County Resolutions, 1967-1968 (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - Education Proposals, 1967-1968 (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - Pending, 1967-1968 (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - Wellsville Legislation Correspondence, 1967-1968 (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - Temporary State Commission to Study the Problems of the Deaf (1 of 2), 1967-1968 (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - Temporary State Commission to Study the Problems of the Deaf (2 of 2), 1967-1968 (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - 1968-1969 Budget (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - Act to Amend Public Health Law, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - Allegany County Resolutions, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - Fredonia University, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 45)
  - Gun Legislation, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 46)
  - Highway Planning and Correspondence, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 47)
  - Joint Legislative Committee to Revise and Simplify Education Law (1 of 2), 1968 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Joint Legislative Committee to Revise and Simplify Education Law (2 of 2), 1968 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Joint Legislative Committee to Revise and Simplify Education Law, ca. 1968 (Oversize 2)
  - Legislation Correspondence, 1968 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Legislative Research (1 of 2), 1968 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Legislative Research (2 of 2), 1968 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Newsletters, 1968 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Office of Legislative Research Report, 1968 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Salamanca, 1968 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - State Taxes Survey and Proposal, 1968 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Timber Harvesting Legislation, 1968 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Welfare - Flat Grant, 1968 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Blaine Amendment, 1968; Undated (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - The Facts About Mayor Lindsay's Liquor Tax Proposal, Undated (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - New York State Commercial Banks in Agriculture, Undated (Box 3, Folder 14)